You know, even animals say, cute.
People who say they're cute, cute, cute...
They don't get attached to cute things either.
That's nice.
He's not too attached to cute things.
So you're the kind of person who can't stop talking.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm a talkative person to begin with.
I'd love to.
I'd love to. That's a relief.
Can you hear Raj?
Sometimes he eats twice a day.
That's a lot.
I got a job.
Masashi.
Part of it is that I really like the taste.
But also because it comes out quickly and it's easy to go alone.
The kettle and the idol
Here they come!
This is Starlust's homogeneously raised kettle kettles!
Today we have another guest, this time an idol.
This is Yuna Suzuki of Starlast Iginari Talk, from the other side of the street.
Yuna Tsukki, from Iginari Talk.
Thank you very much.
This is the fourth guest from Tohoku, following Fujitani, Yasumori and Date.
Yes, that's right.
Yes.
I am the fourth.
The show is going to be cute, but...
I'm sorry.
Not at all.
This way?
Yes, it's a show about being cute.
It's cute... no, it's totally cute, but...
But I don't want to push "cute" to the forefront.
As for self-production...
I'll do anything.
I'm not usually that cute.
Oh, that's right.
That's right. You can tell from the way I look.
It's always rude to say that, but...
No, it's totally fine.
I'm not a cute character.
I'm not obsessed with cute things either.
That's good.
I'm not really attached to cute things.
That's why I often say that I'm not really happy when people say I'm cute.
That's right.
I'm not happy when people say I'm cute.
Even animals are called cute, right?
Anyone who says you're cute and cuddly...
You're saying it to animals, aren't you?
They call everything cute.
I'd be happier if you were more specific.
In detail.
Yes, sir.
That's not easy.
You're asking for more than you think.
No, it's fine.
I'm glad you could make it here today, and I look forward to working with you.
And now, for January's Foot Produce, we're proud to announce the arrival of our Cinderella group.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
How do you like being in a room full of people like this?
I get nervous every year.
Nervous?
Yes... there's a lot of pressure.
Like when we decide who our solo Cinderella idols will be.
We're the group that declared we're going to be Cinderella.
That's why I'm worried about what I'll do if I don't become Cinderella.
I'm the type of person who gets really anxious about what I'll do if I don't become a Cinderella.
I felt like I was going to be crushed by the pressure.
But I think you're more right than any other group in terms of how you want the event to go.
Are you sure?
Really?
I'm the type of person who takes everything seriously.
You're right, and that's why the fans feel the same way.
Fans of other groups are also carried away.
I'm glad to hear that.
But every year, at the Cinderella Festival in January, they get the message.
They get it? Surprisingly.
We get hit pretty hard.
Really?
Do you think it would be better to have a different approach next year?
Yes, like a school festival.
I'd rather not fight anymore.
That's not how I feel about it.
I think it's more interesting to watch them fight.
Yoshida also likes that kind of thing.
I'd like to take that into consideration.
Ah! He's not here right now.
I'm in charge.
Wait a minute.
It's based on trust.
It's my favorite kind of relationship.
It's like a direct exchange of signatures.
Don't you have that?
No, I mean...
No signatures.
That's right.
He asked me if I wouldn't be here today.He was like, "Is it okay if I'm not here for a little while today?
I said, "No problem, I'll take care of it.
I see.
This is quite interesting, isn't it?
I think the relationship between the captain and the members is a little bit different from the others.
I think the relationship between the captain and the members is a little different from the others.
I'm sure you'll find a lot of interesting things if you dig deeper.
I see.
I'm not just a manager.
Of course.
I like to watch him all the time.
I see.
That's why I'm here.
I'd like you to invite the captain to the next Yakanta Idol.
I'd love to.
Just a little...
You know...
I'd like you to go as a sub.
I'd love to have him.
I'd like you to do it.
I'll sign it then.
I always say how interesting it is.
I love it there.
I see.
That exchange...
Yes.
Yes, partly because I really like the taste.
Well, it comes out quickly, and also it's easy to go alone.
This program is Yuna-chan's favorite, Erieli
Jun-san
Morimaru-san
I have something to say, Naosuke.
A-chan, who loves Yuna
This program was brought to you courtesy of
Thank you for everything, everyone!